Abosede Precious IRERUA

1 Iranlowo–Oluwa quarters, Jamade Yidi Apete, Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria. Tel: 08057265346; E-mail: abosedeirerua@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a recent graduate with a degree in Microbiology having intermediate knowledge and skill in information technology. I have proven academic and curricular achievements and possess excellent communication and interpersonal skills with ability to work efficiently in teams. I seek a challenging career with a progressive organization that provides an opportunity to maximize my potentials in achieving organizational goals and objectives.

I am flexible and versatile enough to handle work descriptions outside the scope of my experience.

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Certified Secure Computer User (CSCU)

Microsoft Word packages (PowerPoint, Word and Excel)

CompTIA project

Adobe Dreamweaver 1 and 2.

Excellent oral and written communication and presentation skills.

Highly organized and efficient.

Strong ability to balance multiple priorities with excellent time management skills.

EDUCATION

Health, Safety and Environmental Summit (HSE)

March 2019

Samuel Adegboyega University

Sep 2013 – Jun 2017

Bachelor of Science in Microbiology, 2nd Class Upper (Honours)

Thesis Title: Effect of Human Activities on the Physicochemical and Bacteriological Qualities of Ujigba River, Ujiogba, Edo State, Nigeria.

Publication: Enerijiofi K., Olatunji E. & Irerua, P. A (2018), 'Effect of Human Activities on the Physicochemical and Bacteriological Qualities of Ujiogba River, Ujiogba, Edo State, Nigeria'. Journal of Applied Life Sciences International. 17. 1-8. doi: 10.9734/JALSI/2018/40435.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

National Youth Service Corp (NYSC)

Nov 2017 - Oct 2018

Oyo State Water Corporation

Responsibilities

- Determination of physical properties of well water samples for clients which manufacturing companies and private individuals.
- Preparation water quality report for client
- Maintaining laboratory equipment in proper conditions.
- Maintained weekly inventory of testing supplies.

Abosede Precious IRERUA

26 Road 3, White Sand Beach Estate, Ologolo Road, Lekki, Lagos State, Nigeria. Tel: 08057265346; E-mail: abosedeirerua@gmail.com

Steady Steps School lekki

July 2019- till date

Instructor Responsibilities

- Coordinated various science, technology, engineering and mathematics (S.T.E.M) activities.
- Surpervised different team building activities.
- · Guilded pupils during creative arts and designs.

Faith Mediplex Laboratory

Intern

Mar 2016 - Oct 2016

Responsibilities:

- Performed Gram Stain and microscopic examination of physiological, morphological, and cultural characteristics of bacteria and other micro-organisms.
- Conducted laboratory tests in the areas of haematology, coagulation, urinalysis, serology and immunology.
- Prepared chemical solutions, reagents and specimens for microscopic examination.
- · Prepared reports and analysed findings.

Queen's Supermarket Part time Sales Assistant

Jun 2011 – Oct 2017

Responsibilities:

- Created a friendly and positive shopping environment, with the aim to bring customer satisfaction always.
- Promoted sales by building good rapport with customers.
- Attended to promptly to customers' orders to maximize their experience.
- Restocked the shop regularly and efficiently, including sourcing for goods and communicating with distributors of certain products.

VOLUNTARY SERVICES

NAFDAC Community Development Service

Nov 2017 – Oct 2018

- Assisting NAFDAC in carrying out its function of regulating and controlling the manufacture, importation, exportation, advertisement, distribution, sale and use of food, drugs, cosmetics, medical devises, chemicals and packaged water in Nigeria.
- Sensitization of the general public on national health and drug use.

Ushering and Media Team, Public Event

Jun 2013 - Nov 2017

- Coordinated weekly seating arrangement for both outdoors and indoors programs for about 200 people.
- Decorate venues for special events.
- Keeping account of income generated from fund raising activities and manage the finances of the organization's social media.

Interests: Research, Event planning, volleyball and Catering.